<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stéphane Delbruel</title>
    <link>https://delbruel.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Stéphane Delbruel</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://delbruel.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://delbruel.net/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://delbruel.net/contact/</guid>
      <description>
stephane.delbruel @ kuleuven.be +3216374538 Dpt Computer Science, KU Leuven </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://delbruel.net/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://delbruel.net/projects/</guid>
      <description>A Distributed Federation for LoRaWAN : FLIP This work aims to propose a collaborative platform for LoRaWAN actors.
 Backward compatibility with any deployed Class A end-device Free roaming inside the federation Cheap entry price: 1 Raspberry Pi Participating clusters in various European cities  More resources in the official repository: here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://delbruel.net/pubs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://delbruel.net/pubs/</guid>
      <description>Journals   Simplifying CPS Application Development through Fine-grained, Automatic Timeout Predictions with Stefanos Peros, Sam Michiels, Wouter Joosen and Danny Hughes at ACM Transactions on Internet of Things
  [submitted] Chimera: A low-power reconfigurable platform for Internet of Things with Emekcan Aras, Fan Yang, Wouter Joosen and Danny Hughes at ACM Transactions on Internet of Things
  Conferences   Tackling Contention Through Cooperation: A Distributed Federation in LoRaWAN Space with Nicolas Small, Emekcan Aras, Jonathan Oostvogels and Danny Hughes at International Conference on Embedded Wireless Systems and Networks (EWSN 2020) pdf</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://delbruel.net/sandaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://delbruel.net/sandaw/</guid>
      <description>Academic Service I&amp;rsquo;m actually involved in the co-organization of the 5th ASF GDR Winter school in distributed systems as well as serving as co-chair on the M4IoT workshop (2019,2018,2017) collocated with ACM/IFIP/USENIX Middleware conference. I also served in the Technical Program Committee for DFSD (2020, 2019) as well as Shadow PC member for Eurosys (2019, 2018).
I&amp;rsquo;ve been a visiting researcher at Università della Svizzera Italiana in Switzerland during summer 2016 under the supervision of Pr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last Event</title>
      <link>https://delbruel.net/post/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://delbruel.net/post/news/</guid>
      <description>Our latest article Simplifying CPS Application Development through Fine-grained, Automatic Timeout Predictions will appear in the upcoming issue of ACM Transactions on Internet of Things !</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>