<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stéphane Delbruel</title>
    <link>https://delbruel.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Stéphane Delbruel</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://delbruel.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://delbruel.net/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://delbruel.net/contact/</guid>
      <description>
stephane.delbruel @ labri.fr +33 (0)5 40 00 69 21 LaBRI </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://delbruel.net/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://delbruel.net/projects/</guid>
      <description>DILUTE: Fluid Service Abstraction for Large-Scale Cloud IoT Systems This project address the question of geo-distributed resources management and service placement in the context of fog computing.
More resources on the official webpage: here
A Distributed Federation for LoRaWAN : FLIP This work aims to propose a collaborative platform for LoRaWAN actors.
 Backward compatibility with any deployed Class A end-device Free roaming inside the federation Cheap entry price: 1 Raspberry Pi Participating clusters in various European cities  More resources in the official repository: here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://delbruel.net/pubs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://delbruel.net/pubs/</guid>
      <description>Journals   Simplifying CPS Application Development through Fine-grained, Automatic Timeout Predictions with Stefanos Peros, Sam Michiels, Wouter Joosen and Danny Hughes at ACM Transactions on Internet of Things pdf
  Chimera: A low-power reconfigurable platform for Internet of Things with Emekcan Aras, Fan Yang, Wouter Joosen and Danny Hughes at ACM Transactions on Internet of Things pdf
  Conferences   A Federated Fog-Cloud Framework for Data Processing and Orchestration: A Case Study in Smart Cities with Dapeng Lan, Yu Liu, Amir Taherkordi, Frank Eliassen and Lei Liu at ACM/SIGAPP Symposium On Applied Computing (ACM SAC 2021)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://delbruel.net/sandaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://delbruel.net/sandaw/</guid>
      <description>Academic Service I&amp;rsquo;m actually involved in the co-organization of the ASF GDR Winter school in distributed systems as well as co-chair for the M4IoT workshop (2021,2020,2019,2018,2017) collocated with ACM/IFIP/USENIX Middleware conference.
I have served as a reviewer for IEEE International Conference on Distributed Computing Systems, ACM SIGCOMM Computer Communication Review and IEEE Transactions on Dependable and Secure Computing.
I also previously served in the Technical Program Committee for DFSD (2020, 2019) as well as Shadow PC member for Eurosys (2019, 2018).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last Event</title>
      <link>https://delbruel.net/post/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://delbruel.net/post/news/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
